Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Collection Development, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Associate university librarian for collection development, Yale University, records
1954-2011
RU 124
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
49.75
(55 boxes)
The records consist of subject files of the associate university librarian documenting the growth and development of the Yale University Library's holdings, with a focus on the bibliography department.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-B (YRG 32-B), Records of deputy, associate, and assistant university librarians of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files of the associate university librarian documenting the growth and development of the Yale University Library's holdings, with a focus on the bibliography department.
Academic libraries -- Administration; Academic libraries -- Collection development; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Library
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Collection Development, Yale University, circa 1985-1988, Accession 1989-A-097 (Box 1–4)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Collection Development, Yale University, 1982-1989, Accession 1991-A-006
  - Research Library Group
    - Fees (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Geoscience (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Inter-Library Loan (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Music (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Online Computer Library Center (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Preservation (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Pricing Structure (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Research Library Group: Steering Committee Membership (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Schomburg Center (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Science Citation Index (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Secretary, Office of (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Serials Task Force (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Serials Working Group (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Smithsonian Institution Libraries Optical Disk Working Group (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sterling Memorial Library
    - Move (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Replacement Procedure (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Soft Ware Task Force (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - South Carolina, University of (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Stanford University Library (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Student Services Brochure (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Swiss Embassy (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - System Automation Memo (Box 1, Folder 24 - 25)
    - Tax Reforms (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Tax Reforms: 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Turner Libros, S.A. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - University Microfilms International (UMI) Titles Orders (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - University Council Committee on the Library (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Van Sinderen Prize (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Wired Librarian's Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Yale Computer Center (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Yale University Resource Office for Students and Employees with Disabilities (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Yale University Library: Air Conditioning (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Yale University Library: Equipment Request: Fiscal Year 1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Yale Journals (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Yale University Fringe Benefits (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Yale University Library: Staff Development (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Yale University Library: Undergraduate Internship Program (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Yankee (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Acquisitions Working Group (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bibliography Dept.
    - Bibliographers Meeting, Agenda and Notes (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Bibliography Department (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Bulldog Computers (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Catalogs/Brochures: Computers (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Clerical and Technical Overtime:, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Equipment; General, Memos (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Expense Reimbursements (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - External Relations (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - General (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - International Business Machines (IBM) PC/AT Machine (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Liability of Librarians (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Local 34 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Lubin Business Procedures (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Office Procedure (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Shipping Receipts (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Software (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Staff Attitudinal Survey (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Student Pay Sheets: Used (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Student Wage Budget (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Teleconferencing (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Telephones (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - UPRAS (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Xerox Bills (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Business Department (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Catalog Department (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Catalog: Working Group (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Center for British Art (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Circulation Department: Working Group Task Force (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Classics Library (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Classics Department (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Cross Campus Library (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Divinity Library (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Drama Library (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - East Asian Collection (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Engineering Library (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health Library (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Governmental Documents: Depository Inspection (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Governmental Documents (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Historic Sound Recordings (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - History Department (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - History of Art Department (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Italian Department / Romance Languages and Literatures (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Academic Research Librarian of the Year Award (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Academic Computer Systems Report (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Administrative: Correspondence and Memos (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Administrative: Task force Appointments (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - American Philological Association: Classical Studies on Microfiche Project (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Application Implementation Task Force (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - ACSUS: Association for Canadian Studies (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Association of College and Research Libraries (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Association for Computers and the Humanities (ACH) Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Audio-Visual Resources (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Automation Steering Committee (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - B.B. Blackwell: North America / Reference (Box 2, Folder 100 - 103)
    - Budget, General: Fiscal Year 1987 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Compact Disc-Read Only Memory
    - General (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC) Report (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Production (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Network: The Computer Center, Graduate School and University Center, City University of New York (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - New York Public Library (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - North Carolina, University of (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Northwestern University (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Northwestern Online Total Integrated System (NOTIS)
    - General (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Conversation Specifications (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Implementation (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Online Computer Library Center: Collection Software Analysis (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - On Line Services (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - On Line Services: Chemical Abstracts (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Online Research Bibliographic Information System (ORBIS) (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Oklahoma State University (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Palmaverde (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Performance Expectations, Task Force (Box 3, Folder 121 - 122)
    - Pergamon Press (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Photocopy Licenses (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Plenery (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Preservation / Cooperative Preservation Project (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Professional Activity Support Task Force (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Project, Eli (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Public Relations Task Force (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Research Publications (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Rochester, University of (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Roper Center (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Research Library Group
    - Board of Governors (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Collection Management and Development Committee (CMDC) (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Collection Management and Development Committee: Brown: Fall, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - German Bibliographers (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Research Library Group Conoco (Germany Study), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Judaica
    - Linda P. Lerman Memo and Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Linda P. Lerman Expense Reports Fiscal Year 1988-89 and Travel (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - General (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Sothelrby's Jerusalem (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Kline Science Library (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Latin American Collection (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Map Collection: General (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Maps: Laman Collection (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Medicine, Yale School of: History of Medicine (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Medical Library (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Middle East Studies (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Mudd Library (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Music Library (Box 3, Folder 150 - 151)
    - Music Library (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Near Eastern Collection (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Organization and Management, School of (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Personnel Department (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Reference Department (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Religious Studies, Department of (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Science Department (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Social Science Library (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Yale University Library: Social Science Collection (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - South East Asia Collection (Box 4, Folder 161 - 162)
    - Spanish/Portuguese Departments (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Statistics Library (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Systems Office (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Systems Office:, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Center for Research Libraries (CRL) (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Center for Research Libraries: Foreign Newspaper Microfilm Project (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Center for Research Libraries, COOAP, 1989 September 6 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Clearwater Publishing Company (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Columbia University: Data Base Evaluation Project (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Commission on Preservation and Access (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Computer
    - Software (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - General/Collegiate Microcomputer (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - General/Gridcomm (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - General/Informatics General Computers (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - General/Lettrix (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - General/MMIMS, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - General/Palantir (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - General/Software Publishing Company (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Northwestern Online Total Integrated System (NOTIS) (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Computer: Paradise Systems (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Connecticut Center for the Book Planning Committee (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Deparmental Networking Committee (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Discriminatory Pricing: Articles (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Educational Testing Service (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Electron Service at the Heard Library (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Electronic Bulletin Boards (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Engineering, Council of (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Expensive Items: Reports (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Farmington Plan (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Garland Publishing (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Gordon and Breach (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Grants and Contracts (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Hardware/Software Systems Task Force (HSSTF) (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Harrassowitz, General (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Harvard University Library (HUL Notes) (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Harvester (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Higher Education Price Index (1987 Update) (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Human Resources, Department of (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Humanities Advisory Committee: Yale University (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Humanities Text Bases (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Info World Periodical (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - International Conference on Computers and the Humanities (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - International Federation of Library Associations (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Internship Programs (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Kentucky, University of (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Laprade Collection (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Leadership Development Task Force: Yale University Library (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Library and Information Professionals (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Library Holdings: Comparisons (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Library of Congress
    - Computer Periodicals Currently Received (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - General (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Middle East Cooperative Purchase Plan (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Library Science (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Library Toms, 1988 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Low Papers (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - McAdams Planning Consultants (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Management (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Management Data for Collections Task Force (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Management Information Services: Yale University Library (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Thomas Mann Symposium (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Map Resources Group (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Media Policy (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Michigan, University of: Overlap Study (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Michigan, University of: University Library (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Microcomputer Advising Board (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Microforms International (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Micro Software (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Midwest Approval Plan (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - MRDF: Services (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Music Information Processing Standard (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Social Science Bibliographer: Memos and Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 239)
- Record of Michael Keller as associate university librarian, circa 1985-1993; Accession 1994-A-074
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - RLG Conspectus Worksheet East Asia Collection (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - RLG Conspectus Worksheet Judaica Collection (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - RLG Conspectus Worksheet Latin American Collection (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - RLG Conspectus Worksheet Philosophy and Religion Collection (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - RLG Conspectus Worksheet South East Asia Collection (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - RLG PRIMA (program for Research Information Management) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - RLG Social Sciences (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - RLG Subnational Foreign Government Publications Working Group (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - RLG Verification Study Zola (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - RLG Verification Study Neurology (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Saztec International (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Schmidt Library Purchases (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Selectors' Conference (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Serials cancellations - FY87 and FY88 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Serials +20000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Serial Catalogue Sample Report (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Serial Pricing Discrimination, Misc (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - SML Bco, Umberto (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Travel (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Turner Subscriptions (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - UMI Offer 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Us - RISM Libretto Project (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Wess/Florence April 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Yale Union Negotiations (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - YUL - Newsletter (Nota Bene) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Acquisition Non-Print Acq 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - African Collection (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Afro-American Studies (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Art, School of (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ATLA -Divinity Library (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Germanic Bibliography (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Germanic Lang and Lit (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - American Trust for the British Library (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ARTFL (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ACRL/WESS Conference - Florence, Italy, Apri14-8 1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Book Budget Requests - FY89 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - YUL Book Budget FY89 (current operations) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Book Budget Requests - FY88 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Budget - Serial Expenditures (by selector/FY88) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Budget - General - FY88 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Book Budget/General- FY87 (lacking) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Book Budget/General (RMCP) - FY86 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Budget Pre - FY86 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - University of California Berkeley - General (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Canadian Association of Music Libraries (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Casalini (copies of statements) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - CasaIini Libri (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Center for Computer Assisted Research (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - NEH 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - NOTIS - Planning (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Photocopy Gordon and Breach (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Retrospective Conversion "RECON Background (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - RECON file (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - RECON Inter-date Elements (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - RECON Interrogatory/responses (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Retrospective Conversion Task Force IT (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Retrospective ConverSion Task Force I (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - RECON Task Force Meeting (hand-outs) (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - RECON vendors (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Royalties (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - RLG Conspectus Verification (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - RLG Conspectus Worksheet African Collection (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - RLG Conspectus Worksheet Art and Architecture (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - CRL - CDOAP - October 17, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Computer General/Spires (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Computer HP Graphics Printer/Supplies Ordered (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - CT Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Copyright Permission (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Exchanges (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Expensive Desiderata FY89 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Frankfurter Buchmesse (Frankfurt Book Fair) (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - General Counsel (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - HarrassowitzJBilling 1988 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Human Relations Area Files (lacking) (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Iberbook (lacking) (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Center for the Book (29-31 October 1987)/ LioraIy ofCongress (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Music Library Association Meeting - Feb 9-14 1987 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Italian Music and Lyric Poetty Project (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Schirmer Books (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Wess Paper (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Ferrara (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Harvard University Library/ Credenza file AssJmta Pisani (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Hamilton College (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Italian visit (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Iowa, University of Libraries (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Collection Development Council, 1989/90 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Gifts FY89 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Gifts FY91 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Gifts in Kind (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Harrassowitz Correspondence 1989/90 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Harrassowitz Dam, Richard (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Harrassowitz Statements, July-December 1989 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Harrassowitz Statements, January-June 1990 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Harrassowitz Statements, July-December 1990 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - ILL 1985/86 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - ILL 1988/1989 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Imprint Dates Completed Random Sample (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Imprint Dates Random Sample, Shelf Space (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Kline Science library Book Budget Requests FY91 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Kline Science Library Increases in '87 Journals (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Kline Science Library Science Journals (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Mainframe Database Committee (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - MAK Notes and Dnifts (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - MAK Calendar 1992 - (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Manuscripts and Archives I (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - ManuscriPts and Archives II (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Manuscipts and Archives Republication of Lindbeqh's We (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Manuscripts and Archvies Search (Head) (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Medical library Search for Collection Management and Asst Historical Librarian (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Nedbook Correspondence 1989 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - A and A Facility (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - African Collection 1989 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - African Collection 1990 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - iAfrican Collection 1991 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Anthropology Library (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - IBeinecke Library 1989-91 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - lChemistry Library (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Divinity LIbrary - FY89 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Divinity Library - FY90/91 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Divinity Library - FY91/92 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Divinity Library - FY91/92 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Divinity library - FY91/92 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Divinity Librmy, Annual Report - Rough Draft (Dec 1991) (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Divinity Library - ATLA Divinity Library" Tweedy Center (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Divinity Librarian Search - Oct 1991 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - East Asian Collection I (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - East Asian Collection Proposal - FY91 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Japanese Studies Proposal- FY91 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - East Asian Collection (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Forestry LIbrary - (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Historical Sound Recordings Archive (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - HSR- Warren (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Holocaust Testomonies - Video Archive (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Latin American Collection (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Music library -1989-91 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Administration Conference (Ad Con) (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Administration - General (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Administration - Travel (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Apple (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Appraisal and Disposal of Donated Property document (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - APSIA (Association of Professional Schools of International Affairs) (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Association of American University Presses (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - BH BlaCkwell 3-Year Price Comparison Report (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Cambridge University Reporter (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Collection Development - Payroll Distribution, July 1991 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Commision Restructuring Faculty Arts and Sciences (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Computer Science (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - CRL Annual Meeting - Apri11992 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - CRL Paper April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Economics Department (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Expensive Serials Project (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Faculty Talk on Collection Development - March 1992 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Fire Alarm Zones (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Fiscal Support Group (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - French Revolution FY90-91 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Fulbright Program of UK - Potential candidates (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - House Diaries (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Idaho State Library (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Joint Project of Libraries of SUNY Albany, Binghamton, Buffalo, Stony Brook (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Lady Stewart (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Library of Congress - Cataloguing Distribution Service (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Matter Archives Project (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Medical Ltbrary Journal Cancellations, July 1988 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Nedbook Correspondence 1990 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Norman Ross Publishing (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Nota Bene (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Pergamo and Elsevier - Series Study (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Perseus 1.0 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Physics Department (Yale University) (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Plakatbucher (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Professional Literature Collection - FY89 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Providence Group (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Psychology Department (Yale University) (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Rainbow Reports (August - December 1990) (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Serials - Duplicate Serials Cancellations (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Telephone Directories (Box 5, Folder 186)